pointandpay.net 2016-04-08

# Point & Pay, LLC ("Point & Pay") Privacy Policy | Point & Pay

###  Security Information and Privacy

Point & Pay is committed to the privacy and security of personal information obtained from visitors to [www.pointandpay.com](http://www.pointandpay.com/). The following policies ensure your personal information is secure.

###  What This Policy Covers

This policy covers Point & Pay's treatment of personally identifiable information collected when you visit [www.pointandpay.com](http://www.pointandpay.com/). This policy does not cover any other Point & Pay-owned sites or any sites operated by Point & Pay on behalf of our clients. Information collected by Point & Pay on sites operated on behalf of our clients is covered by their respective customer privacy policies.

###  Information Collection and Use

####  Aggregate Information

Upon visiting [www.pointandpay.com](http://www.pointandpay.com/), Point & Pay's Web server automatically:

  * Sends a session ID cookie to your computer
  * Collects your IP address
  * Collects information about your Internet Service Provider
  * Collects information about the browser you use

Using the site's Web server log files, Point & Pay reserves the right to use cookies and IP addresses to analyze trends, track visitors' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Cookies and IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information, such as your email address, but may reveal the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our site or not), and what operating system you are using. Cookies expire when you leave the site.

###  Personal Information

Point & Pay will not share any personal information you make available to us for any marketing or solicitation purposes, although it may be used by Point & Pay for these purposes. When you click on a link to email Point & Pay, we may collect information that identifies you personally, such as your email address and name, which we may use to contact you. If you attach any documents to your email, such as a resume for employment purposes, Point & Pay may use that information to contact you.

###  Information Sharing and Disclosure

Point & Pay will not disclose to any third parties any of the information collected during your visit to our [www.pointandpay.com](http://www.pointandpay.com/) site, except in response to government or law enforcement related inquiries.

###  Updates and Effective Date

Point & Pay may amend this policy from time to time. If any substantial changes are made in the way your personal information is collected or used, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on [www.pointandpay.com](http://www.pointandpay.com/).

This Privacy Policy was updated on January 20, 2007.

###  Questions or Suggestions

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [info@pointandpay.com](mailto:info@pointandpay.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy).
